Hey y'all and welcome back to Living in
Central Texas. I'm Andrea Dudik and
today we are touring my newest listing
[music] in Belton ISD. Priced at
$324,900.
[music] This home offers just under
$1,900 ft of living space. [music] It's
4 bed, two bath. It was built in 2019,
so it has a very like new [music] feel.
and it sits on a spacious third of an
acre lot, which is super awesome for
this price [music] point. Now, something
I really appreciate about this home is
that it was built by a super reputable
builder, really known for attention to
detail and quality craftsmanship, and
you can really feel that throughout
[music] this home. Let's go take a look.
The layout is open to the kitchen and
dining, but pulled back [music] just
enough that it still feels intentional,
which is perfect when you're
entertaining and don't want the kitchen
to be the main focus. [music]
This builder really shines in the
details. Some of his signature touches
like accented wood detailing in the
ceilings [music] and wood look ceramic
tile flooring may cost a little bit more
upfront, but they truly elevate the home
and make it [music] feel more custom.
The kitchen is bright and functional
with white cabinetry, yards of granite
countertops, a tile [music] backsplash,
a corner walk-in pantry, and a brand new
stove. It's a space that works just as
[music] well dayto-day as it does when
hosting. Okay, y'all. I love this
kitchen. [music] I really think it's the
focal point of the home. It opens up
really seamlessly [music]
to the main living space. It's bright.
It's tastefully done. You have your
two-tone cabinets, both white, and then
the blue island. Granite countertops,
stainless steel appliances. The
backsplash is super cute. I love it.
What do you think? Let me know in the
comments below.
The main living space also features
crown [music] molding and a wood paneled
electric fireplace, adding warmth and
character without feeling overdone.
There are three goodsized secondary
bedrooms served by a bath with custom
cabinetry and modern ceramic tile.
The primary suite is a standout with a
decorator ceiling, deep garden tub,
separate tiled [music] shower, double
sinks, and two closets, which buyers
always love.
Outside you [music] have full saw and
inground sprinkler system, privacy
fencing, and don't forget a.33 acre lot,
which is hard to find in this price
[music] point.
If you're looking for a thoughtfully
built home in [music] Belton ISD,
roughly 10 minutes from MLAN Children's
Hospital in Baylor Scott and [music]
White with quality design, an amazing
layout, and so much to offer, this one's
definitely worth an in-person look. If
you'd like more information on this
home, a private tour, or just
information on relocating to the Central
Texas area in general, I'd love to help.
Don't forget to subscribe and follow
along so that you can stay uptodate on
all things real estate here in central
Texas. Till [music] next time.